A Guide to the YMCA of Greater Richmond Records, 1854-2019 (bulk 1920-1998)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Research files- Chronological, 1855-2004, 2.1 cu. ft. (6 boxes); Boxes 13-18.
  - 1940-1949 Documents (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
  - 1950-1959 Documents (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1960-1969 Documents (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1970-1979 Documents (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  - 1980-1989 Documents (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - 1990-1999 Documents (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - 1990-1999 Documents (Box 17, Folder 1-9)
  - 1990-1999 Documents (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - 2000-2004 Documents (Box 18, Folder 5-8)
- Series III: Research files- Subject files, 1854-2004 (bulk 1965-1995), 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes); Boxes 19-28.
  - Act of Incorporation and Sketch of YMCA History, 1854-1856 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Agreements and deeds (4th and Franklin St.), 1884-1887 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Agreements and deeds (6th and Main St.), 1885-1886 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Agreements and deeds (6th and Main St.), 1890-1900 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Agreements and deeds (7th and Grace St.), 1905-1907 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Agreements and deeds (7th and Grace St.), 1908-1919 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Agreements and deeds, Camp Richmond (Charles City, Va.), 1932-1936 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Agreements and deeds, Camp Richmond (Charles City, Va.), 1938-1958 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Agreements and deeds, Camp Richmond (Charles City, Va.), 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Branches, Chamberlayne Ave. Property (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Branches, Chester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Branches, Chester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Branches, Chester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Branches, Chester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Branches, Chickahominy Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Branches, Downtown Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Branches, Downtown Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Branches, Downtown Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Branches, Downtown Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Branches, Manchester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Branches, Manchester Family YMCA (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Branches, Chester Family YMCA, History timeline board (Box 20a)
  - Branches, Manchester Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Branches, Midlothian Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Branches, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Branches, Patrick Henry Family YMCA (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Branches, Patrick Henry Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Branches, Patrick Henry Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Branches, Patrick Henry Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Branches, Patrick Henry Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Branches, Shady Grove Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Branches, Shady Grove Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Branches, Shady Grove Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Branches, Shady Grove Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Branches, Shady Grove Family YMCA (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Branches, Short Pump Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Branches, Southside Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Branches, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Branches, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Branches, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Branches, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Branches, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Branches, Research (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, Family Communicator, 1989-2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Railroad Men, 1909-1916 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Railroad Men, 1917 (Box 23a, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Railroad Men, Misc., 1903-1912 (Box 23a, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1901 (Box 23a, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1911 (Box 23a, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1912 (Box 23a, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1913 (Box 23a, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1914 (Box 23a, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1915 (Box 23a, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1916 (Box 23a, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, Richmond's Young Men, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Y News 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, Y News, 1971-1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1883-2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Annual report, 1856-1864 (Box 24)
  - Publications, Annual report, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Annual report, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Annual report, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Annual report, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Annual report, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Annual report, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Annual report, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Annual meetings, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Calendars, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Dedication, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Flyers, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Marketing, c. 1950-1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Railroad Men, 1915-1916 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Camps (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Chronology (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Chronology, Final (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Ed Crews, Drafts (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Ed Crews, Notes (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Drafts (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Drafts (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Drafts (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Fact checked chapter (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Final chapter drafts (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," History Committee (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Interview prospects (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Layout (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Leadership (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Jim Leiby notes (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," MCV (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," William Munford (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Muscular Christianity (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Notebook (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Notes (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Proposal (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Railroad YMCA (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Research, John McCaffrey (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Barry Taylor interview (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," 2003 Milestones (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - "The Richmond YMCA," Richmond's Y's Mens (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Oversize papers (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Series IV: Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks, 1910-2003 (bulk 1985-2001), 6.85 cu. ft. (14 boxes); Boxes 29-41a.
  - Clippings, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, Tuckahoe Family YMCA, 1941-1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1956-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, Brookland Family YMCA, 1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, Chesterfield Family YMCA, 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Camp Weyanoke, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1985 November-1989 December (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1988 January-August (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1988 September-December (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1989 January-March (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1989 April-May (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1989 June-July (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1989 July-August (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1989 September-October (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1989 November-December (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1990 January-March (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1990 February-1995 November (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1990 March-April (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1990 May (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1990 June (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1990 July (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1990 August-September (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1990 September (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1990 September-October (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1990 November-December (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1991 January-February (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1991 March-April (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1991 May-July (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1991 August-September (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1991 October-December (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1992 January-February (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1992 February-March (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1992 April-May (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1992 May-June (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1992 July (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1993 January-April (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1993 April-June (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1993 June-August (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1993 September-October (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1993 November-December (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1994 January-February (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1994 March (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1994 April-May (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1995 January-February (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1995 March-April (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1996 February-1999 September (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1996 February-April (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1996 May-July (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1996 August-September (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1996 October-December (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1997 January (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1997 February (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1997 March-April (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1997 May-June (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1997 July (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1997 August (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1997 September (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1997 October (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1997 November (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1997 December (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1998 January-February (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1998 February (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1998 March (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1998 April (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1998 May (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1998 June (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1998 June-December (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1998 July (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Tuckahoe Family YMCA, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1999 January-April (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1999 February (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1999 March (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1999 April-May (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1999 June-July (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1999 August-October (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 2000 February-2003 August (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, nd (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Oversize Clippings, 1968-2000 (Box 39a)
  - Scrapbooks, 1960-1966 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbooks, 1963 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbooks, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbooks, 1910 (Box 41)
  - Scrapbooks, 1926-1928 (Box 41)
  - Scrapbooks, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
  - Scrapbook, 1974-1985 (Box 41a)
- Series V: Photographs, 1854-2004 (bulk 1950-1990), 10.5 cu. ft. (20 boxes); Boxes 42-61.
  - Subseries 1: Chronological files, 1854-2004 (bulk 1910-1990), Boxes 42-48.
    - 1854-1859 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 1860-1869 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - 1870-1879 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 1880-1889 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 1900-1909 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1910-1919 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 1910-1919 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - 1920-1929 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - 1920-1929 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - 1930-1939 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - 1940-1949 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 1950-1959, Health club (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - 1950-1959, Sports/Gym (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - 1950-1959, Spots/Gym (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - 1950-1959, South Richmond site dedication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 1960-1969, Awards ceremony (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 1960-1969, Northside Camp, Boys (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1969, Northside Camp, Boys (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1969, Northside Camp, Girls (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1969, Dance (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Basketball (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Fencing (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Handball (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Handball (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Karate (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1969, Sports, Swimming (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1970-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1970-1979, Camp (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1970-1979, Dedication (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1970-1979, Sports (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 1970-1979, Sports (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - 1970-1979, Sports, Handball (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - 1980-1989 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 1980-1989, Buildings (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1980-1989, Heritage Club (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 1988, Event (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - 1990-1999, Album (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - 1991, Heritage Club (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - 1994, 140th Anniversary (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - 2000 June (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - 2000-2004 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - 2000-2004 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Buildings, nd (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Library of Virginia copies, nd (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Valentine Museum photo archives, nd (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Valentine Museum copies, nd (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2: YMCA Branches, 1950-2001 (bulk 1990-2000), Boxes 48-50.
    - Chester Family YMCA, c. 1990 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Chester Family YMCA, Groundbreaking, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Chester Family YMCA, 1990-1999 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Chickahominy Family YMCA, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Chickahominy Family YMCA, Groundbreaking, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Chickahominy Family YMCA, 1990-1999 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Crestview Christmas Party, 1990-1999 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Downtown Family YMCA, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Downtown Family YMCA, Dedication, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Downtown Family YMCA, Dedicatin, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Downtown Family YMCA, c. 1960-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Manchester Family YMCA, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Manchester Family YMCA, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Midlothian Family YMCA, Groundbreaking, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Midlothian Family YMCA, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - North Richmond Family YMCA, Halloween, c. 1980s (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - North Richmond Family YMCA, c. 1950-1960 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - North Richmond Family YMCA, Track team, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Patrick Henry Family YMCA, c. 1980s (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Patrick Henry Family YMCA, Groundbreaking, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Patrick Henry Family YMCA, Christmas wrap fundraiser, c. 1980s (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Petersburg Family YMCA, Playground, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Shady Grove Family YMCA, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Shady Grove Family YMCA, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Tuckahoe Family YMCA, c. 1980s (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Tuckahoe Family YMCA, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Tuckahoe Family YMCA, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Tuckahoe Family YMCA, c. 1990s (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Tuckahoe Family YMCA, Expansion, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 18a)
    - Miscellaneous Family YMCA, 1970-1990 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Camp Thunderbird, c. 1980-1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Camp Thunderbird, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Partnership Founding, Germany, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3: Staff, 1940-2000 (bulk 1980-1990), Boxes 50-52.
    - Board of Directors, c. 1940-1950 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors, c. 1960-1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors, c. 1980-1990 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors, c. 1990-2000 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors, Meeting, c. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors, Chairman Round Table, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Staff annual giving training, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Staff, c. 1980-2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Staff, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Volunteers, c. 1980-2000 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 4: Subject files, 1970-2000, Boxes 52-53.
    - Adults and families, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Children, c. 1980-2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Children, c. 1980-2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Children, c. 1980-2000 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Christmas pagent, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Computer training, c. 1980 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Emblem slides, nd (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Exercise, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Group shots, c. 1980-1990 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Group shots, c. 1990 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Halloween, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Heritage Club Presentation, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Indian Guides, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Kinder Kollege, 1989-1994 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - James A. Leiby retirement party, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - National Guard, c. 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Refugee program in Sudan, c. 1984 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Poster negatives, nd (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Self defense class, c. 1980-1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Seniors, c. 1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Seniors, c. 1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Teens, c. 1980-1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - YNOT Party, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Unknown (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Unknown (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Unknown (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Slides, cds, and oversize, Boxes 54-61.
    - Slides, Facilities, 1970-1998 (Box 54)
    - Slides, Miscellaneous, 1978-1992 (Box 55)
    - Photographs on posterboard, c. 1920-1970 (Box 56)
    - Photographs on posterboard, 1970-1990 (Box 57)
    - Cds, 1986-2004 (Box 58)
    - Cds, 1986-2004 (Box 59)
    - Framed oversize photographs, 1880-1937 (Box 60)
    - Oversize photographs, 1935-1990 (Box 61)
  - Subseries 6: Presidents, Box 62.
    - Presidents and chairs, 1955-2019 (Box 62)
- Series VI: YMCA Library, 7 cu. ft.
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1982 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1983 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1984 (3 copies) (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1985 (2 copies) (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1986 (2 copies) (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1987 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1990 (2 copies) (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1991 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1992 (2 copies) (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 198 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1998 (Volume On shelf)
  - Statistical Summary and Analysis, 1999 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1932 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1934 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1936 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1937 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1938 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1939 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1940 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1942 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1943 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1945 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1946 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1947 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1948 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1958 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1959 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1960 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1962 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1963 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1964 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1965 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1966 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1967 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1968 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1969 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1971 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1972 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1973 (Volume On shelf)